Guide to the Oehrlein and Associates Architect records, 1981-2007 MS2294
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Oehrlein & Associates Architects records
1981-2007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Oehrlein, Mary L.
Oehrlein & Associates
MS2294
68.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains architectural drawings (both oversize and letter file size), photographs, negatives and reports. The firm began in 1984, but the records date from 1981-2007. These records document the work this firm undertook in historic preservation Washington DC Metropolitan area.
Arrangement
Organized into 2 series: Architectural drawings (oversize tubes) and Project files.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains architectural drawings (both oversize and letter file size), photographs, negatives and reports. The firm began in 1984, but the records date from 1981-2007. These records document the work this firm undertook in historic preservation in the Washington DC Metropolitan area.
Biographical / Historical
Mary L. Oehrlein established this Washington architectural and preservation firm in 1984. Oehrlein & Associates Architects specialized in historic preservation, adaptive reuse, renovation and additions and alterations. The type of jobs most often involved government buildings, multi-unit residential, museums, offices, park buildings, and religious facilities. Prior to opening the firm Oehrlein was director of the Washington office of the Ehrenkrantz Group/ Building Conservation Technology. The office closed in 2011 when Oehrlein began working for the Architect of the Capitol.
Historic preservation; Architects; Architecture; Architecture -- Washington (D.C.)
- Architectural drawings (oversize tubes), 1982-2006; Series 1; 45 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the architectural drawings created and collected by Oehrlein & Associates Architects for the architectural projects completed from 1982-2007.
  - 1001 Pennsylvania Ave, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 87)
  - 1001 Pennsylvania Ave NW, 1987; Series 1 (Tube 83)
  - 1001 Pennsylvania Ave Roll 1, 1984; Series 1 (Tube 7)
  - 1001 Pennsylvania Ave Roll 2, 1984; Series 1 (Tube 8)
  - 1001 Pennsylvania Ave Roll 3, 1984; Series 1 (Tube 9)
  - 1001 Pensylvania Ave, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 92)
  - 810 7th St NW (Sq. 428), Undated; Series 1 (Tube 75)
  - 901 F St NW, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 5)
  - All Souls Church, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Tube 67)
  - Almas Original Construction Drawings, 1924; Series 1 (Tube 26)
  - Almas Temple 13th and K St NW Dismantled/Moved, 1993; Series 1 (Tube 3)
  - Anderson House, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 72)
  - Atlantic Coastline Building, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 14)
  - Atlantic Coastline Railroad Building 601 Pennsylvania Ave, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 15)
  - Auditors Main Building, 1993; Series 1 (Tube 65)
  - Auditors/Departmental/Agriculture Building Elevators, 1985; Series 1 (Tube 71)
  - Carnegie Institution 1530 P St NW, 1997; Series 1 (Tube 1)
  - Chicken Out [2/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 61)
  - Chicken Out, 4866 Mass Ave [1/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 60)
  - East Potomac Park, Driving Range and Pro Shop [1/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 41)
  - East Potomac Park, Driving Range and Pro Shop [2/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 42)
  - East Potomac Park, Golf Cours Cart Pavilion, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 40)
  - East Potomac Park, OAA Historic, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 43)
  - Elizabeth Arden, 1147-1147 Connecticut Ave NW, 1985; Series 1 (Tube 24)
  - Ellipse Visitor Pavilion, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 70)
  - Evening Star, 11th and Pennsylvania Ave, 1987; Series 1 (Tube 57)
  - Franklin School, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 51)
  - Franklin School Construction Sketches and Review Drawings, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 49)
  - Franklin School DC School Alterations, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 50)
  - Franklin School Preliminary Drawings, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 48)
  - Gallery Row, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 91)
  - Gallery Row [1/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 54)
  - Gallery Row [2/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 55)
  - Gallery Row Mall Kiosks, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 52)
  - Gallery Row Struc/Mech?elec, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 53)
  - Gallery Row, 410-417 7th Street NW, photogramentry mylars, reduced façade drawings, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 31)
  - Gallery Row, 410-417 7th Street NW, preliminary sketches and sepias, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 32)
  - Gallery Row, 410-417 7th Street NW, Roll 1, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 30)
  - Gallery Row, 410-417 7th Street NW, Roll 2, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 33)
  - Grant Building, US Soldiers' and Airmen's Home, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 25)
  - Hecht and Co., 7th and E Streets NW, Historic Drawings, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 29)
  - Homer Building, 601 13th St NW, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 78)
  - Homer Building, 601 13th St NW Originals/Shop Drawings, 1986; Series 1 (Tube 77)
  - Howard Hall (bid), Undated; Series 1 (Tube 44)
  - Howard Hall Misc., Undated; Series 1 (Tube 47)
  - Howard Hall Project Record Drawings, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 45)
  - Howard Hall Restoration, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 46)
  - Hyattsville Armory "Castle", Hyattsville, MD, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 36)
  - Kiosks on the Mall, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 39)
  - Langston Golf Course, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 11)
  - Lansburghs, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 27)
  - Lincoln Memorial Kiosks, 2007; Series 1 (Tube 64)
  - Lincoln Square [1/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 81)
  - Lincoln Square [2/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 82)
  - Lincoln Square Demolition [1/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 93)
  - Lincoln Square Demolition [2/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 94)
  - Lincoln Theater, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 79)
  - National Airport Historic Dining Room, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 17)
  - National Geographic, 1993; Series 1 (Tube 19)
  - Natural History Rotunda, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 66)
  - Old Administration Building, Arlington National Cemetery, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 6)
  - Otto, Shernick, Miller Maryland State Monument, Antietam National Battlefield, MD, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 23)
  - PADC DWGS 817-819-821 - Market Space (not in sq. 457-c scope), Undated; Series 1 (Tube 16)
  - PAPC 819-821 Market Square, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 12)
  - PAPC PEPCO Substation Historic Facade, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 10)
  - Real Estate Trust Building, 1333 H Street, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 28)
  - Ritz Carlton, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 56)
  - Ritz Carlton, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 58)
  - Ritz Carlton Hotel, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 59)
  - Rock Creek Park Golf Course, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 13)
  - San Francisco Plantation, Reserve, LA, 1975; Series 1 (Tube 34)
  - SEFC Historic Drawings 158, 159, 187, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 76)
  - Shakespeare Theater, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 73)
  - Smithsonian Castle Windows, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 37)
  - Sq. 488, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 86)
  - Strathmore Hall, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 22)
  - Straus Fountain, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 18)
  - Sumner School, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 89)
  - Sumner School [1/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 62)
  - Sumner School [2/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 63)
  - The Castle, Hyattsville, MD, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 38)
  - The Westory, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 84)
  - The Westory Building, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 2)
  - Tiny Jewel Box, 1143 Connecticut Ave NW, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 35)
  - US Department of Treasury Cash Room, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 74)
  - Washington Monument Renovation, 1999; Series 1 (Tube 4)
  - Westory Building, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 85)
  - White House Visitor Center [1/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 68)
  - White House Visitor Center [2/2], Undated; Series 1 (Tube 69)
  - White House Visitors Center Ceiling Rehab, Baldridge Hall, Commerce Buulding, 1987; Series 1 (Tube 88)
  - White House Visitors Center in Commerce Department, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 90)
  - Women in Military Service in America Memorial, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 80)
  - Woodies Marquee, 1935; Series 1 (Tube 20)
  - Woodward and Lothrop, Undated; Series 1 (Tube 21)
- Project files, 1981-2007; Series 2
  This series contains the project files for Oehrlein & Associates Architects for the architectural projects completed from 1981-2007.
  - 1001 Pennsylvania Avenue--421 11th Street, 1987; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General Note
    Type of work: Restoration/Compatible Storefront Design Address: 1001 Pennsylvania Ave NW Original date of construction: 1909/1920s Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - 1001 Pennsylvania Avenue--418 10th Street, 1987; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1001 Pennsylvania Avenue--425-429 11th Street, 1987; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1001 Pennsylvania Avenue--423 11th Street, 1987; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1001 Pennsylvania Avenue--421-431 11th St. NW, 1987; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1001 Pennsylvania Avenue--Photos/Negatives, 1987; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1143 Connecticut Ave/Tiny Jewel Box [1 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 1143 Connecticut Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1915 Clark Waggeman Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - 1143 Connecticut Ave/Tiny Jewel Box [2 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1147 Connecticut Ave/Elizabeth Arden, 1987; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 1145-47 Connecticut Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1929 Mott B. Schmidt Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - 1147 Connecticut Ave/Elizabeth Arden [1 of 3], 1987; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1147 Connecticut Ave/Elizabeth Arden [2 of 3], 1987; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1147 Connecticut Ave/Elizabeth Arden [3 of 3], 1987; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1427-29 Rhode Island Avenue NW, 2003; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Documentation Address: 1427-29 Rhode Island Ave NW, WDC Folder contains photographs:
  - 1439 Rhode Island Avenue NW, 2001; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Type of work: Documentation Address: 1439 Rhode Island Ave NW, WDC Folder contains photographs:
  - 2501 Pennsylvania Avenue NW/The Luzon--drawings, 1989; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Type of work: Documentation Address: 2501 Pennsylvania Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1896 Nicholas Haller Folder contains drawings
  - 2501 Pennsylvania Avenue NW/The Luzon--photos, 1989; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Type of work: Documentation Address: 2501 Pennsylvania Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1896 Nicholas Haller Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - 313-315-317 9th St NW/Fed Triangle, 1981; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Documentation Address: 313-315-317 9th Street NW, WDC Folder contains photographs:
  - 3245 O Street NW (demolished '97), 1997; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Documentation Address: 3245 O Street NW, Washington DC Folder contains photographs:
  - 504-512 10th St NW, 1990; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Design Address: 504-512 10th Street NW, WDC Folder contains photographs:
  - 708/716 Jackson Place-Trowbridge House, 2005; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Repairs and Improvements Address: 708-716 Jackson Place NW, WDC Folder contains photographs:
  - 800 7th Street block/633-635 H Street NW, 2005; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Research and Building Evaluation Address: 800 7th Street block/633-635 H Street NW, WDC Folder contains photographs:
  - 901 F Street (now Gallup Building) [1 of 2], 1993; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 901 F Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1870 Cluss & Kammerheuber Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - 901 F Street (now Gallup Building) [2 of 2], 1993; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 901 F Street, 1993; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - All Souls Unitarian Church, 1988; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Master Plan for Repairs and Capital Improvements Address: 2835 16th Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1924 Coolidge, Shepley & Bulfinch Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - All Souls Church, 1988; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Almas Temple/One Franklin Square, 1990; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Dismantling/Reconstruction Address: 1315 K Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1929-1930 Allen Hussell Potts Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Almas Temple, 1990; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Almas Temple photos [1 of 4], 1990; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Almas Temple photos [2 of 4], 1990; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Almas Temple photos [3 of 4], 1990; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Almas photos, 1990; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Almas Temple RC prints, 1990; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Arts & Industries Building Smithsonian, 1985; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Inspection Mid-Term Report Address: 900 Jefferson Drive, SW, WDC Folder contains photographs
  - Arts & Industries Building Smithsonian photos and CDs [1 of 2], 1999; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Arts & Industries Building Smithsonian photos and CDs [2 of 2], 1999; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Atlantic Coastline Railroad Building [1 of 2], 1986; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Dismantling/Reconstruction Address: 601 Pennsylvania Ave NW, DC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1890 James G. Hill Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Atlantic Coastline Railroad Building [2 of 2], 1986; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Auditors Main Building, 1993; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Roof Replacement Address: 14th & Independence Ave SW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1880 James G. Hill Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Bethesda Theatre, Inform Awards Submission, 2007; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Address: 7719 Wisconsin Ave, Bethesda, MD Original date of construction: 1938 Folder contains large photographs
  - Bethesda Theatre, VA/DC AIA Awards Submission, 2007; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bethesda Theatre, Research/Articles/Miscellaneous, 2007; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bolling Air Force Base [1 of 4], 1991; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Type of work: Environmental Assessment Address: McDill Blvd SE, WDC Original date of construction: 1918 Folder contains photographs
  - Bolling Air Force Base [2 of 4], 1991; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Bolling Air Force Base [3 of 4], 1991; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Bolling Air Force Base [4 of 4], 1991; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Bond Building, 1986; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 1400 New York Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1901 George S. Cooper Folder contains photographs
  - Bowen Building, 2005; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 875 15th Street NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1922 Folder contains photographs
  - Bowen Building, 2005; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Cardozo High School, 2003; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation/Renovation Address: 1200 Clifton Street NW, WDC Folder contains photographs
  - Carnegie Institution [1 of 2], 1999; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation/Renovation Address: 1530 P Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1910 Carrere & Hastings Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Carnegie Institution [2 of 2], 1999; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation/Renovation Address: 1530 P Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1910 Carrere & Hastings Folder contains photographs
  - The Castle/Smithsonian Institution, 1990; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Window and Masonry Restoration Address: 1000 Jefferson Drive SW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1855 James Renwick Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - The Castle blueprints, 1990; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Chicken Out Restaurant, 1995; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Rehab of Esso gas station into restaurant Address: 4866 Massachusetts Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1936 Gordon MacNeil Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Commerce Building, 1999; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Prospectus Development Study Address: 14th & Constitution Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1932 York & Sawyer Folder contains reports and photographs
  - Commerce Building [1 of 2], 1999; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Commerce Building [2 of 2], 1999; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Cooper Houses, 1990; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Documentation Address: 2521-2523 K Street NW, WDC Folder contains photographs/HABS:
  - Cooper Houses--HABS photos, 1990; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - DAR Constitution Hall, 2002; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Type of work: Design of ADA Ramp Address: 18th and E Streets NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1929 John Russell Pope Folder contains photographs
  - Dept of Agriculture/Cotton Bldg., 1994; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Paint Analysis Address: 300 12th Street SW, WDC Folder contains photographs
  - Dept of Justice Modernization [1 of 4], 2006; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Restoration/Rehabilitation Address: 950 Pennsylvania Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1934 Zantziner, Borie & Medary Folder contains report and drawings and photographs
  - Dept of Justice Modernization [2 of 4], 2006; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Dept of Justice Modernization [3 of 4], 2006; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Dept of Justice Modernization [4 of 4], 2006; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Dresden Condominium, 1995-2001; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 2126 Connecticut Ave NW, WDC Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - East Potomac Park, 1995; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Type of work: New driving range, pro shop, upgrades Address: 972 Ohio Drive SW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1916 Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - East Potomac Park Seawall [1 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Address: 972 Ohio Drive SW, WDC Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - East Potomac Park Seawall [2 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Ellipse Visitor Pavilion [1 of 3], 1992; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Type of work: New construction Address: 15th & Pennsylvania Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1994 Oehrlein & Assoc Folder contains drawings
  - Ellipse Visitor Pavilion [2 of 3], 1992; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Ellipse Visitor Pavilion [2 of 3], 1992; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Evening Star Building, undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Address: 1101 Pennsylvania Ave, NW, WDC Folder contains photographs
  - Federal Reserve Board, 1993; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Condition Survey/Specifications Address: 20th & Constitution Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1937 Paul P. Cret Folder contains photographs
  - Franklin School, 1991; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Exterior Restoration Address: 925 13th Street NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1865-69 Adolph Cluss Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Franklin School, 1991; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Franklin School Research [1 of 2], 1991; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Franklin School Research [2 of 2], 1991; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Franklin School 5" x 7" photos, 1991; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Franklin School 8" x 10" photos, 1991; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Franklin School miscellaneous photos, 1991; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Franklin School "before" photos [1 of 2], 1991; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Franklin School "before" photos [2 of 2], 1991; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Franklin School photos [1 of 2], 1991; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Franklin School photos [2 of 2], 1991; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Gallery Row, 1986; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Type of work: Dismantling/Reconstruction of historic facades; design of period storefronts Address: 401-415 7th Street NW, DC Original date of construction: 1860-1883 Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Gallery Row (407-3 7th Street), 1986; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Gallery Row (401 7th Street -- D St), 1986; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Gallery Row (415 7th Street), 1986; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Gallery Row (417 7th Street), 1986; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Gallery Tower/Place/ Square 453, 2005; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Research, Preliminary design Address: 7th and H Streets NW, WDC Folder contains photographs and report
  - Glenwood Cemetery Chapel, 1995; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Address: 2219 Lincoln Road NE, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1892 Glenn Brown Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Grant Bldg/US Soldiers & Airmens Home, 1992; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Type of work: Historic Structures Report/ Rehabilitation Design Address: 3700 N. Capitol Street NW, WDC Original date of construction: 1911 Folder contains drawings and photographs
  - Grant Bldg/US Soldiers & Airmens Home photos [1 of 2], 1992; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Grant Bldg/US Soldiers & Airmens Home photos [2 of 2], 1992; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Greyhound Bus Terminal, 1985; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Type of work: Conditions Survey for Rehabilitation Address: 1100 New York Ave NW, DC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1940 William S. Arrasmith Folder contains original building specs and photographs
  - Greyhound Bus Terminal specifications, 1985; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - GSA-Agriculture South - Historic Structures Report (HSR), 1986; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: 14th & Independence Ave SW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1930-36 Louis A. Simon Folder contains photographs
  - GSA-Custom Serivce Building - HSR, 1986; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: 1331 Pennsylvania Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1935 Arthur Brown Folder contains photographs
  - GSA-Department Auditorium - HSR, 1986; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: 1301 Constitution Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1935 Arthur Brown Folder contains photographs
  - GSA-Federal Trade Commission - HSR [1 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: 6th and Pennsylvania Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1937 Bennett, Parsons & Frost Folder contains photographs
  - GSA-Federal Trade Commission - HSR [2 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - GSA-Interstate Commerce Commission Building- HSR, 1988; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Type of work: Rehabilitation Guidelines Address: 1201 Constitution Ave NW, WDC Original date of construction and Original architect: 1935 Arthur Brown Folder contains photographs
  - GSA-Interior Building - HSR [1 of 2], 1988; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)